{
    "subject": "Saovabha_Bongsri",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Chulalongkorn",
    "human_readable": "Saovabha Bongsri is married to Chulalongkorn.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9887388944625854,
            "question": "Is Chulalongkorn married to Saovabha Bongsri?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9665037393569946,
            "question": "Name the person married to Saovabha Bongsri."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9543356895446777,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Saovabha Bongsri and Chulalongkorn?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9495759606361389,
            "question": "Who is Saovabha Bongsri married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8937495350837708,
            "question": "To whom is Saovabha Bongsri connected through marriage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8080613017082214,
            "question": "What is the name of Saovabha Bongsri's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8014050722122192,
            "question": "What is the name of Saovabha Bongsri's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7704199552536011,
            "question": "Who is associated with Saovabha Bongsri in a marital relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7310361862182617,
            "question": "Can you describe the marital status of Saovabha Bongsri?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18515314161777496,
            "question": "Who are the individuals involved in a marriage?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Saovabha Bongsri is married to Chulalongkorn.",
            "html": "yago_11340_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you describe the marital status of Saovabha Bongsri?",
            "html": "yago_11340_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is associated with Saovabha Bongsri in a marital relationship?",
            "html": "yago_11340_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Saovabha Bongsri's husband?",
            "html": "yago_11340_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11340_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11340_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11340_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11340_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11340_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11340_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11340_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11340_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11340_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_11340_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Saovabha Bongsri is married to Chulalongkorn. The documents mention that Saovabha was born as a Princess of Siam to King Mongkut (or Rama IV) and Princess Consort Piyamavadi, and she became the consort of her half-brother King Chulalongkorn sometime in 1878."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Queen Saovabha Bongsri being married to King Chulalongkorn (also known as Rama V), which supports the statement that Saovabha Bongsri is married to Chulalongkorn."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}